// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "var",
      "let",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "document.write()",
      "console.log()",
      "window.alert()",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "in",
      "is in",
      "exists",
      "lies"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
    answer: "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.",
    options: [
      "The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers.",
      "Clear all the cookies and cache.",
      "Both A and B.",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
    answer: "Object-Oriented",
    options: [
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Object-Based",
      "Procedural",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
    answer: "stringify()",
    options: [
      "stringify()",
      "parse()",
      "convert()",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "JavaScript code can be written in ____.",
    answer: "JavaScript file and in HTML document directly",
    options: [
      "JavaScript file (.js file)",
      "JavaScript file and in HTML document directly",
      "In style sheets (.css file)",
      "HTML document directly"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In JavaScript, what do we use for calling the expression for function definition?",
    answer: "Function literal",
    options: [
      "Function literal",
      "Function prototype",
      "Function declaration",
      "Function calling"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In JavaScript, single line comment begins with ___.",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      "#",
      "/*",
      "$",
      "//"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The 'function' and 'var' are known as:",
    answer: "Declaration Statements",
    options: [
      "Keywords",
      "Data Types",
      "Declaration Statements",
      "Prototypes"
    ]
  }
];